My Monitor Change Log

v2.0
Added ChangeLog file
Improved performance by switching to Where() and ForEach() methods instead of cmdlets
Added Computername property to output. It is not displayed by default.
Added check to see if process used as termination flag is already running.
Added support for categories. See the updated About_MyMonitor file and Measure-WindowTotal help examples.
added MIT license
